const data = [
    {
        question: 'What is the first letter of the Alphabet?',
        guesses: ['D','A','Q','B'],
        correctAnswer: 'A'
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter A?',
        guesses: ['Z','R','C','B'],
        correctAnswer: 'B',
        incorrectAnswers: [
            'R','C','O'
        ]
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter B?',
        guesses: ['C','N','K','D'],
        correctAnswer: 'C'
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter C?',
        guesses: ['A','R','D','B'],
        correctAnswer: 'D'
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter D?',
        guesses: ['F','E','D','Z'],
        correctAnswer: 'E'
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter E?',
        guesses: ['O','J','D','F'],
        correctAnswer: 'F'
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter F?',
        guesses: ['N','M','G','F'],
        correctAnswer: 'G'
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter G?',
        correctAnswer: 'H',
        guesses: ['O','H','M','V']
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter H?',
        correctAnswer: 'I',
        guesses: ['H','Q','I','B']
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter I?',
        correctAnswer: 'J',
        guesses: ['B','K','J','X']
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter J?',
        correctAnswer: 'K',
        guesses: ['N','J','K','M']
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter K?',
        correctAnswer: 'L',
        guesses: ['N','M','O','L']
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter L?',
        correctAnswer: 'M',
        guesses: ['O','M','F','G']
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter M?',
        correctAnswer: 'N',
        guesses: ['N','M','H','D']
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter N?',
        correctAnswer: 'O',
        guesses: ['S','O','C','K']
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter O?',
        correctAnswer: 'P',
        guesses: ['O','O','P','S']
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter P?',
        correctAnswer: 'Q',
        guesses: ['Q','U','V','T']
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter Q?',
        correctAnswer: 'R',
        guesses: ['A','Y','T','R']
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter R?',
        correctAnswer: 'S',
        guesses: ['U','S','E','F']
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter S?',
        correctAnswer: 'T',
        guesses: ['T','M','N','K']
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter T?',
        correctAnswer: 'U',
        guesses: ['I','X','U','S']
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter U?',
        correctAnswer: 'V',
        guesses: ['L','W','V','H']
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter V?',
        correctAnswer: 'W',
        guesses: ['A','V','W','C']
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter W?',
        correctAnswer: 'X',
        guesses: ['X','L','R','W']
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter X?',
        correctAnswer: 'Y',
        guesses: ['S','O','P','Y']
    },
    {
        question: 'What comes after the letter Y?',
        correctAnswer: 'Z',
        guesses: ['Z','B','D','U']
    },
    {
        question: 'GAME OVER',
        correctAnswer: 'Z',
        guesses: ['Hope','You','Had','Fun']
    }
]

export default data;